Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- E, Series V
  - Education: General
    - Reports, etc: E-02.01.02/0018- E-02.01.02/0041, 1985 Jun- 1988 Jul (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Statistics regarding schools, pupils and teachers in Nepal; Education Quarterly; Reports; Seconded village teachers' seminar; Teaching in Nepal; Comments on VSO Education conference
    - Reports, etc: E-02.01.02/0042- E-02.01.02/0060, 1988 Nov- 1990 Nov (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Including regarding: UMN involvement in Village Schools over 30 years; Fact sheet on education; Education Seminar; UMN's role in education; Education seminar report; Suggestions for Nepal's education system
    - Reports, etc.: E-02.01.02/0003, 1983 Jun 5-9 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: National Workshop on Education Innovation
    - Reports, etc.: E-02.01.03/0001- E-02.01.03/0015, 1991 Mar- 1992 Feb (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Including regarding: Vision for UMN education department; Education seminar, minuets and evaluation; Values in Education; Suggestions for National Education Commission
    - Reports, etc.: E-02.01.03/0016- E-02.01.03/0026, 1992 Apr- 1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: Education department circular; Education consultation; Guidelines for writing annual reports; Report of EC
    - Reports, etc.: E-02.01.03/0027- E-02.01.03/0039, 1993 Nov- 1995 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Education department strategic plan; Education department briefing; Overview report; UMN Education update; Friends of Education
    - Reports, etc.: E-02.01.03/0040- E-02.01.03/0050, 1996 Jan- 1998 Sep (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Agreement regarding secondment of personnel to MOE; Emerging issues of education; Education week seminar; Friends of education; Data gathering guidelines for ED projects
    - Reports, etc: E-02.01.03/0051- E-02.01.03/0058, 1998-1999 Aug (Box 50, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Papers on education institute; Update and plans; Overall report; Education week seminar
    - Reports, plans, etc. (E-02.01), 1997-2004 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Education Department publications (E-02.01): "Aiming at the Future" by David McConkey; "Meeting Primary Education Needs of UMN Expatriate Children", 1992, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: E-02.02.01, 1967-1989 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: (E-02.02) inquiries re. UMN funding for schools, 1999-2000 (Box 253, Folder 13)
    - Education Board Meetings: E-02.03.01 - RESTRICTED, 1976-1987 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Education Board minutes: E-02.03, 1976-1987 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - E.B. SOWRs: E-02.04.01/0001- E-02.04.01/0005 - RESTRICTED, 1975-1986 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - ESO: Special Education: E-02.05.01/0001- E-02.05.01/0017, 1979 Dec- 1991 Oct (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Correspondence with Jeanette Short; Write-up on proposal; Proposed agreement with HMG; Seminar on hearing impairment in children; Study materials for the blind; Talking book service and library proposal
    - ESO: Special Education: E-02.05.01/0018- E-02.05.01/0027, 1992- 1996 Nov (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Computer training for the blind; Correspondence about a pre-school for the deaf; Annual Plan; Special education pilot training program; Correspondence with Disabled Welfare Association
    - ESO: Library Consultant: E-02.06.01/0001- E-02.06.01/0016 - RESTRICTED, 1980-1991 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Work program of LC; Detailed report; Grants of books; Reports; Overview of librarians within UMN; Provision of mini-librarians to village schools; Certification of library staff working under HMG/CTEVT
    - ESO: Library Consultant: E-02.06.01/0017- E-02.06.01/0024 - RESTRICTED, 1993-1996 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Negotiations with CTEVT and University; Summary and detailed report; Strategic plan and strategies; Annual report; Annual plan
    - Education: School Courses by UMNers: E-02.07.01/0001-E-02.07.01/0008, 1952-1985 (Box 52, Folder 3-8)
      Including: Science for Elementary Schools in Nepal; Early science course, Gorkha; Vocational agriculture; Physical education; Moral Science; Industrial Arts
    - Education: School Courses by UMNers - "Science in Ten" :E-02.07.01/0006, 1980 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Education: School Courses by UMNers - "Science in Eight": E-02.07.01/0007, 1980 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Education: School Courses by UMNers - "Teaching Maths to Large Classes in Nepal": E-02.07.01/0009, 1985 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Education: School Courses by UMNers - "Oral English": E-02.07.01/0010, 1987 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Education office: E-02.08.01, 1980-1987 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Radio Education: E-02.09.01, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Requests from Schools: E-02.10.01, 1963-1998 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - ESO: Teacher Training: E-02.11.01/0001- E-02.11.01/0023 - RESTRICTED, 1983-1989 (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
    - ESO: Village Schools, Pokhara: E-02.12.01 - RESTRICTED, 1982-1987 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - ESO: Teachers' Christian Fellowship: E-02.13.01/0001- E-02.13.01/0003 - RESTRICTED, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Council for Technical Education- Vocational Training: E-02.14.01/0001- E-02.14.01/0054, 1978 -1997 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
      Including regarding: Trade school outline; New Training and Vocational Education Board; Writing of materials; Certification and testing; Staffing and levels of positions; CTEVT rules; Strategy for CTEVT; Forestry education in technical schools in Nepal
    - Council for Technical Education - Vocational Training - CTEVT Profile: E-02.14.01/0042, 1994 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - ESO: Higher Education: 10 + 2 Village School Partnership Program: E-02.15.01/0001- E-02.15.01/0039, 1983- 1999 (Box 52, Folder 9-11)
      Including regarding: Project proposal for Regional Schools of an international standard; Notes on 10 + 2 discussions; HSEC brochure; Concept proposal; Major issues; Copy of agreement; Annual progress report; Summary plan and action plan
    - Higher Education and 10+2 School Partnership Programme: Reports, plans, etc. (E-02.15), 1999-2006(?) (Box 198, Folder 1)
      See also Dullu, D-07 and Syanjya, S-11
    - Curriculum Development: E-02.16.01/0001- E-02.16.01/0012, 1992-1999 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: National meeting on school maths curriculum; Annual reports; Disappointment about maths course
    - Curriculum Development - Framework for revision of School Maths curriculum: E-02.16.01/0002, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Curriculum Development - Maths book for Class 7, Part 1: E-02.16.01/0008, 1993 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - ESO: Basic Primary Education: E-02.17.01/0001- E-02.17.01/0010, 1991 Jul- 1994 Aug (Box 53, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: Possible ways of assistance with primary education; Meeting at BPEP; Meetings of education consultation members; Concept proposal; Primary school management training and teacher enrichment
    - Basic Primary Education / Enrichment: Reports, plans, etc. (E-02.17), 2000-2003? (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Other E
    - Election of Executive Director, etc.: E-03.00.01/0001-E-03.00.01/0008 - RESTRICTED, 1996-1999 (Box 53, Folder 11-14)
      Executive Director; Treasurer; Personnel Secretary; Education Secretary; Economic Development Secretary; Engineering and Industrial Development Secretary/Director; Rural Development Secretary/Director; Health Services Secretary/Director
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.01/0001 - E-04.00.01/0046 - RESTRICTED, 1962-1981 (Box 54, Folder 1-4)
      Re. salary scales, employment policies, travel rules, etc.
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.02/0001 - E-04.00.02/0034 - RESTRICTED, 1981-1985 (Box 54, Folder 5-9)
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.03/0001 - E-04.00.03/0032 - RESTRICTED, 1985-1990 (Box 55, Folder 1-6)
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.04/0001- E-04.00.04/0055 - RESTRICTED, 1990-1992 (Box 55, Folder 7-12)
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.05/0001 - E-04.00.05/0061 - RESTRICTED, 1992-1998 (Box 56, Folder 1-6)
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.05/0062 - RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Employment Matters: E-04.00.06 - RESTRICTED, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Employment Matters: General (E-04.00) - RESTRICTED, 1997-2004 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Employment Matters: Staff Association (E-04.00)- RESTRICTED, 2000-2004 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Executive Director Letters: (E-05.02) - RESTRICTED, 2002-2004 (Box 198, Folder 5)
      Earlier materials were not received with collection because of their designation as confidential
    - Executive Director Letters to colleagues, staff (E-05.03), 1997-2007 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Executive Director Letters to Member Bodies, Board Members and Partners (E-05.04), 2001-2005 (Box 198, Folder 7)
      Continued from —02
    - Evangelical Free Church of Finland: E-06.00.01, 1961-1991 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Church in America: E-07.00.01, 1968-1987 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Ethics: E-08.00.01/0001 - E-08.00.01/0018, 1971- 1991 Jun (Box 53, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Policy guidelines on business practice, BTI Board action; Ethical guidelines for business and industrial relations; Eight case studies; Forum for discussion and study of development ethics and philosophy
    - Evacuation/ Emergencies: E-09.00.01/0001- E-09.00.01/0030 - RESTRICTED, 1962 Nov- Jun 1998 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: UMN position and line of action, first emergency guidelines; Revised guidelines; Letters regarding Tansen strike situation; Proposal for Pokhara; Political unrest; INF contingency plans; Emergency procedures
    - Evacuation/ Emergencies: E-09.00.01/0031 - RESTRICTED, 1998 Jul (Box 56, Folder 9-11)
      Including regarding: Response to the present political climate, Gorkha
    - Episcopal Church: E-10.00.01, 1964-1974 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Establishment of UMN: E-11.00.01/0001, 1953- 1954 Sep (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Correspondence with all missions, and finalising of first Constitution and by-laws
    - Establishment of UMN: E-11.00.01/0002 - E-11.00.01/0005, 1949-1954 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Accounts of establishment and early days; Correspondence with Nepal-Border Fellowship and related missions; Correspondence between VM, UPC and IMC 1952-1953; Correspondence of Carl and Betty Anne Friedericks 1952-1954
    - Engineering and Industrial Development: E-12.00.01/0001 - E-12.00.01/0049, 1987 -1999 (Box 57, Folder 3-7)
      Including regarding: Proposals for Administrative assistant to EIDS; Division of EID responsibilities; Future EIDS team; EID issues for EC; Inservice training for supervisory staff; Division of responsibilities in EIDD office
    - Engineering and Industrial Development: general / reports (E-12.00), 1999-2005 (Box 198, Folder 8-9)
    - Engineering and Industrial Development Department: leaflet: "Industrial Development Large and Small" (E-12.00), 1991 (Box 252, Folder 15)
    - Enterprise Support: Reports, etc. (E-013.01), 2002-2004 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Enterprise Support: Correspondence (E-013.02) - RESTRICTED, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Enterprise Support: Technical reports (E-013.03), 2003- (Box 199, Folder 2)
- F, Series VI
  - Financial Matters
    - Financial Matters: F-01.00.01/0001 - F-01.00.01/0039, 1960 Apr- 1980 Jan (Box 57, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Explanation of genera and capital fund policy at workers conference; Business Manager's meeting and recommendations; Currency values; PCG policy; Payment of personal bills; Summary of bank accounts; Rules regarding bank accounts; Nepal recorder; Minimum billable accounts
    - Financial Matters: F-01.00.01/0040 - F-01.00.01/0079, 1980 Jan- 1983 Sep (Box 57, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Inflated prices; Funding situation; Banking policies in South Africa; Sources of capital funding; Statement of UMN foreign funds; Personal money matters; Rules regarding handling foreign currency; Use of PCG, FC decision; Insurance; Rules regarding grants of donations for UMN projects; Appeals for funding
    - Financial Matters: F-01.00.01/0080 - F-01.00.01/0127, Oct 1983-1990 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: Financial structure, progress report; General procedures on finances; Guidelines for cash handling in UMN; Funding situation details; Money matters update; Rules for grants and donations to UMN projects; Details of bank accounts; New banking arrangements; Details of investments
    - Financial Matters: F-01.00.01/0128 - F-01.00.01/0159, 1990 Nov-1997 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      Including regarding: Budgeting for staff training and development costs; Task Force paper; PCG rules circulated again; Revised PCG policy; Bad debts write off procedure; Insurance; Proposal for a fund raising policy and comments; Funding situation; Business Managers' conference report; Exchange rates
    - Financial Matters: F-01.00.01/0160 - F-01.00.01/0166, 1998- 1999 Dec (Box 57, Folder 12)
      Including regarding: Details of Finance Department operation; Payment of VAT; Banking details; Funding needs; Proposal for major gift fund; Business Managers' Seminar
    - Financial Matters: Reports, etc. (F-01.00), 1999-2005 (Box 199, Folder 3-4)
    - Financial management framework (F-00), 2009 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Finnish Evangelical Lutheran Mission
    - Correspondence: F-02.00.01, 1975 Oct- 2001 Jan (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: (F-02.00) - RESTRICTED, 2003 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Fellowship House
    - Minutes: F-03.00.01, 1980-1984 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Friends of Shanta Bhawan
    - Correspondence and planning: F-04.00.01, 1981-1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records
    - Grants received by projects: F-06.00.01/0001 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Grants given by donor agencies: F-06.00.01/0002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Expenditures by projects; Miscellaneous correspondence with donors not on other files: F-06.00.01/0003 - F-06.00.01/0004 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- G, Series VII
  - Gandaki Boarding School, Pokhara
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.01/0001 - G-01.01.01/0021, 1965 Dec- 1968 Jun (Box 58, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Visit to school site and notes on meetings; Proposed Boys' Boarding School near Pokhara, report to UMN Board; Notes on opening and beginnings; Board minutes and appendices; Approved policy of employment, etc.
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.01/0022 - G-01.01.01/0039, 1968 Nov- 1971 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Mountain School; Board minutes, etc.; Prospectus for 1969; Notes on Boys' Boarding School in Pokhara; Job description for Headmaster; Scholarship program; Swimming instructions
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.01/0040 - G-01.01.01/0066, 1971 Sep- 1976 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Lindell's circular letter; Extra-curricular enrichment activities; Plan for teaching English in this school; Track and field sports, etc.; A description of NAV; Letter to parents; School house activities; Making the Boys' Boarding School in Pokhara
    - Reports,etc. - School calendar: G-01.01.01/0058, 1973 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.01/0067 - G-01.01.01/0084, 1976 May- 1982 Jan (Box 58, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: Staff quarters, duties of teacher, etc.; Hostel diet; Field study program outline; Participation of UMN in GBS; Comments on draft evaluation; Letter to Min. of Education regarding strikes, etc. New rules for Community Private Boarding Schools
    - Reports, etc.- Final evaluation report: G-01.01.01/0077, 1978 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Reports, etc. - School report / magazine: G-01.01.01/0078, 1978 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.01/0085 - G-01.01.01/0099, 1982 Feb- 1985 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      Including regarding: Letter regarding Girls' Boarding School; Students' strike; Meetings about Regional School; Regional school hostels and leadership training; Agreement for regional school
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.02/0001 - G-01.01.02/0024, 1985- 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: School calendar for 1985; Plans for school bus and health centre; Proposed Constitution for Ex-Student' Association; Breakdown of scholarship scheme details; Staff list for term 2; Evaluation paper for teachers; Community service club; School calendar for 1986
    - Reports, etc. - Annual school magazine: G-01.01.02/0020, 1985 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.02/0025 - G-01.01.02/0040, 1986 Apr- Dec (Box 59, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Health Centre; Selection of scholarship students; Report on Term 1; Listing of Academic staff; School bus obtained; Annual report for UMN; Library report; Need for girls' hostel; HM report for school year
    - Reports, etc.-: G-01.01.02/0031, G-01.01.02/0039 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.02/0041- G-01.01.02/0054, 1987-1987 Jul 2 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      Including regarding: Details of scholarships and staff training; Policy of employment; School calendars; Daily routine; Report on Science Fact-Finding Mission; HM report on Term 1
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.02/0055- G-01.01.02/0067, 1987 Jul 15- 1988 Jun (Box 59, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: GBS and the regional system; New admissions in 1988; School calendars; Listing of student composition; HM report on Term 1; Academic staff list Term 2
    - Reports,etc.- Prospectus: G-01.01.02/0060, 1988 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.02/0068- G-01.01.02/0081, 1988 Sep- 1989 Jul (Box 59, Folder 5)
      Including regarding: H.M. report on Term 2; Principal's report for 1988; New admissions for 1988; School magazine and calendar; Need for second girls' hostel; Student numbers; Plans for teacher training; Summary of schools' history for UMN 35th anniversary booklet
    - Reports, etc- School magazine.: G-01.01.02/0073, 1988 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0001- G-01.01.03/0021, 1990 Jan- 1992 Apr (Box 59, Folder 6)
      Including regarding: Visit of King and Queen; Policy of employment and PF rules; Demands from local community and agreement; Visit to GBS; GBS profile; Scholarship funding; Future planning of GBS
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0009 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0022- G-01.01.03/0041, 1992 Jul- 1993 Oct (Box 59, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Work experience for Class 10 students; Duties of HM; Newsletter; Letter on evaluation; Principals' report; School magazine; Appeal for teachers; GBS profile; Detailed annual report
    - Reports, etc.- School magazine: G-01.01.03/0031, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0042- G-01.01.03/0060, 1993- 1995 Mar (Box 59, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Principals' reports; Correspondence on anonymous letters; Circular to parents; Management committee minutes; Summary Annual Plan
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0061- G-01.01.03/0085, 1995 May- 1997 Aug (Box 59, Folder 9)
      Including regarding: Letter to parents; SLC results; Occasional letter to friends of GBS; Summary report; Discussion paper at UMN education department reporting day; Student work experience; Key features of LTP; Scholarship program; Funding for bus; School magazine
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0073, G-01.01.03/0082, G-01.01.03/0088, 1995-1997 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Reports, etc.: G-01.01.03/0086- G-01.01.03/0104, 1997 Aug- 2000 Jan (Box 59, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: Scholarship circular and leaflet; School magazine for 1997; Guidelines for teachers; Appeal for funding for water supply; Problems for UMN in GBS; GBS annual reports; Overview; Acting Principal position
    - Reports, etc.: (G-01.01), 1999-2004 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Annual magazines: (G-01.01, 2002-2004 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: G-01.02.01/0001- G-01.02.01/0024 - RESTRICTED, 1965 -1974 (Box 60, Folder 1-5)
    - Correspondence: G-01.02.02/0001- G-01.02.02/0030 - RESTRICTED, 1974-1986 (Box 60, Folder 6-10)
    - Correspondence: G-01.02.03/0001- G-01.02.03/0013 - RESTRICTED, 1987-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence: (G-01.02) - RESTRICTED, 2003-2007 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Management committee (Joint GBS & GCES) - RESTRICTED, 2003-2007 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture/Farm: G-01.03.01/0001- G-01.03.01/0027, 1968-1982 (Box 61, Folder 4-6)
      Including regarding: Outlines and plans of work; Application for grant; Report on agriculture work; Proposed development through 1970; Proposed plans for agriculture work program at completion; Two reports; "Nepali Ideal School"
    - Building: G-01.04.02 - RESTRICTED (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Building Program: G-01.05.01/0001- G-01.05.01/0015, 1966-1975 (Box 61, Folder 8-11)
    - Building Program: G-01.05.02/0001- G-01.05.02/0017, 1973 -1993 (Box 62, Folder 1-5)
    - College of Engineering and Science: Reports (G-01.06), 2000-2006 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - College of Engineering and Science: Correspondence (G-01.06) - RESTRICTED, 2002-2007 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - College of Engineering and Science: Publications, prospectus, magazine (G-01.06), no date (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Gorkha Project
    - General: Reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.01/0001- G-02.01.01/0009, 1956- 1958 Apr (Box 62, Folder 6)
        Including regarding: Original outline for Community Service Program; Copy of agreement; Primary school constitution; The Gorkha story; Annual report; School statistics
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.01/0010- G-02.01.01/0037, 1958 Dec- 1969 May (Box 62, Folder 7)
        Including regarding: Plans sent to Planning Committee; Reports; Purchase of trees for building; Letters regarding mailbags and freight; Severe rice shortage; Notes on school matters; Teachers' weekend course; Project minutes
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.01/0038- G-02.01.01/0046, 1970 Aug- 1972 Dec (Box 62, Folder 8)
        Including regarding: Details of schools, prior to handover; Plan for hydropower microplant; Reports on CHP; Report of Teacher's Health Seminar
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.01/0047- G-02.01.01/0065, 1973 Nov- 1982 Apr (Box 62, Folder 9)
        Including regarding: AP Hospital to continue; Brief description of hospital to CIDA; Financing of hospital; CHP report; Project objectives; CHP proposal; Reports on surgery, health education and training; Report on water projects
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.01/0066- G-02.01.01/0083, 1982 May- 1984 Jan (Box 62, Folder 10)
        Including regarding: Report on workshop on role and future of CHP; Hospital statistics breakdown; Nutrition seminar two reports; Working rules for project, Hospital and CHP; Hospital statistics; Nutrition Advisor's report; Proposed water project rules and insurance scheme; Future of Rural Development in Gorkha; Statistics and reports
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.02/0001- G-02.01.02/0009, 1983 Sep- 1984 Nov (Box 63, Folder 1)
        Including regarding: PMC minutes for hospital and CHP; Survey of nursing services with statistics and recommendations; CHP maps; Study of outpatient records; Future of AP hospital
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.02/0010- G-02.01.02/0030, 1984 Dec- 1986 Jun (Box 63, Folder 2)
        Including regarding: Hospital financial figures for analysis; PMC minutes for hospital and CHP; NFE visit report; Information for new doctors; PMC minutes for joint project; Nurse aide training outline; Survey of staff departures
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.02/0031- G-02.01.02/0049, 1986 Sep- 1987 Sep (Box 63, Folder 3)
        Including regarding: Report of health improvement at Thalaying; Detailed hospital report; PMC minutes for hospital and CHP; RDC visit report; CHP circular; Detailed annual plans; Information sheet for short termers; NFE visit report
      - Reports, etc.: G-02.01.02/0050- G-02.01.02/0062, 1987 Sep- 1989 Jan (Box 63, Folder 4)